_Search Icon_ 

[

](https://mobilecitizen.org/)

_Search Icon_ 

Privacy Policy
==============

**Mobile Citizen Online Privacy Policy**

Effective Date: January 31, 2020

This Privacy Policy describes how Mobile Citizen, LLC (“we”, “us”, or “Mobile Citizen”) protects your privacy when you use our website located at mobilecitizen.org (our “Website”). This Privacy Policy applies only to personal information collected through our Website or through e-mails sent to us. “Personal information” means information that identifies you or other people personally, either alone or in combination with other information available to us. This Privacy Policy is part of and incorporated into our Website Terms of Use.

**Your Consent to This Privacy Policy; Contact Us**

By using our Website, you are agreeing to the collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy, you may not use our Website. **If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, please send an email to us at [customerservice@mobilecitizen.org](mailto:customerservice@mobilecitizen.org).**

**This Privacy Policy May Change**

We reserve the right to update or modify this Privacy Policy, at any time and without prior notice, by posting the revised version of this Privacy Policy on our Website. Your use of our Website following any such change constitutes your agreement that all personal information collected from or about you through our Website after the revised Privacy Policy is posted will be subject to the terms of the revised Privacy Policy. You may access the current version of this Privacy Policy at any time by clicking on the link marked “Privacy Policy” at the bottom of each page of our Website.

**What Personal Information Do We Collect on Our Website?**

Information You Volunteer. We collect the personal information you knowingly and voluntarily provide when you use our Website. For example, we collect the information you provide when you register on our Website, complete the “Contact Us” or “Getting Started” form on our Website, or otherwise voluntarily provide information to us. In addition, if you have signed up for the Mobile Citizen wireless broadband service (the “Service”), when you complete your registration process online, the information you provide (which may include your name, billing address, credit card number, email address, or other information) may be provided directly to our Service provider and shared with Mobile Citizen.

Information Sent to Us by Your Web Browser. We may collect information that is sent to us automatically by your web browser, such as your IP address, the address of the web page you were visiting when you accessed our Website, information on your operating system and browser, and the date and time of your visit. The information we receive depends on the settings on your web browser. The information provided by your browser does not identify you personally. We use this non-personal information primarily to create statistics that help us improve our Website and our business. However, if you have created a user profile by registering on our Website, we may link the information provided by your browser to information that identifies you personally. In addition, we may review our server logs for security purposes, such as detecting intrusions into our network. If we suspect criminal activity, we might share our server logs — which contain visitors’ IP addresses — with the appropriate investigative authorities who could use that information to trace and identify individuals.

Information Collected Using “Cookies” and Other Web Technologies. Like many websites, we may use “cookies,” and similar technologies to collect information and manage our Website. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web server. Cookies cannot be used to install computer programs or deliver viruses to your computer. We may use cookies to collect information about the ways visitors use our Website or to facilitate your interactions with our Website. If you do not wish to receive cookies, you may set your browser to reject cookies or to alert you when a cookie is placed on your computer. You may also delete our cookies as soon as you leave our Website.

**How Do We Use Your Personal Information?**

We use the personal information collected through our Website to provide information you may request, to respond to your inquiries, to improve our Website, to provide you with certain information or updates regarding the Service, for billing purposes, and for any other applicable purposes related to our business. We may, from time to time, use your personal information to send you information we believe may be of interest to you. We also use your personal information for security and fraud prevention purposes, to better understand our guests, to better market and advertise our services, and for other purposes as we may disclose to you at the time that we collect your personal information or to which you subsequently consent.

**With Whom Do We Share Your Personal Information?**

Related Entities and Trusted Third Parties. We may share personal information collected through our Website with our current or future affiliates, subsidiaries, parent company, or related entities (collectively, the “Mobile Citizen Affiliates”), or with companies and organizations that perform services on our behalf. Examples of organizations that provide services on our behalf include companies that provide data management, data storage, web hosting, or email services. We will not share your information with third parties (other than Mobile Citizen Affiliates or vendor’s providing services to Mobile Citizen) for their marketing purposes without your permission, except as described in this Privacy Policy.

Anonymous or Aggregated Information. Mobile Citizen reserves the right to create and share aggregate reports on user demographics, Website traffic, and usage information with third parties administering advertising programs on our Website (“Third Parties”). We may inform these Third Parties of our analyses of our server logs, including details regarding Website usage and general information about our Website users. However, such disclosures will refer only to general, aggregate usage data from these analyses – never specific identifying information. This may allow these Third Parties to provide advertisements that are pertinent to our users’ needs, or to provide improvements to the Service or marketing thereof. Because we don’t track usage patterns in a manner which can be identified to individual users, no Third Party will ever have the right to know that a specific user clicked their ad or profile.

Legal Compliance and Safety. We and the Mobile Citizen Affiliates may disclose the personal information collected through our Website when we or they, in good faith, believe disclosure is appropriate to: (i) comply with the law (or a court order or subpoena); (ii) prevent or investigate a possible crime, such as fraud or identity theft; (iii) enforce the Website Terms of Use or other agreements that govern your use of our Website; (iv) respond to your requests for customer service; (v) protect the rights, property or safety of Mobile Citizen, the Mobile Citizen Affiliates, any of our users or others; or (vi) to protect your vital interests.

Successor Entities. Information submitted to our Website is an asset of Mobile Citizen and will become part of our normal business records. Your personal information and other data collected by us may be transferred to another company that has acquired the assets of Mobile Citizen or any of the Mobile Citizen Affiliates, as the result of a sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution, liquidation or otherwise. If such a transfer occurs, the acquiring company’s use of your personal information will still be subject to this Privacy Policy, and the privacy preferences you have expressed to us (although the acquiring company may revise this Privacy Policy after the acquisition).

Modifying or Deleting Your Information. We respect your right to make choices about the ways we collect, use and disclose your personal information. You may update or modify your information, or request that we delete your information from our databases, at any time by visiting the “Contact Us” section of our Website or by sending an email to us at customerservice@mobilecitizen.org.

**Transfer of Data Abroad**

If you are visiting this Website from a country other than the countries in which our servers are located (currently USA) the various communications will necessarily result in the transfer of information across international boundaries. By visiting our Website and communicating electronically with us, you consent to the processing, storage and transfer of your data as set out in this policy.

**Third-Party Website Privacy Practices**

Our Website may contain links to third-party websites and/or databases that are not operated by us (including without limitation those operated by or for our Service provider). These links are provided for your reference and convenience only and do not necessarily imply any endorsement of the activities of these third-party websites nor any association with their operators. We do not control these websites and we are not responsible for their data practices. We urge you to review the privacy policy posted on any websites you visit before using the websites or providing any personal information about yourself. When you complete your online registration for the Service, the data you provide may be submitted directly to our Service provider and will be subject to their privacy policy (in addition, if our Service provider shares such data with us, that data will also be subject to this Privacy Policy).

**Children’s Privacy**

Our Website is not intended for users under the age of 18, and we will not knowingly request personal information from or market to children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, do not provide us with any personal information. If we learn that someone under 13 has provided personal information to our Website, we will use reasonable efforts to remove such information from our databases.

**Security**

Mobile Citizen uses industry-standard firewall and password-protection systems to protect its networks, and only authorized individuals have access to the personal information provided by our Website’s users. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and modified as necessary. However, please note that no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure. As a result, we cannot guarantee the security of the information that you transmit via our Website.

[

](https://mobilecitizen.org/)

Copyright © Mobile Citizen, a Voqal Partners project. All Rights Reserved. [Terms of Use](https://mobilecitizen.org/terms-of-use/) | [Privacy Notice](https://mobilecitizen.org/privacy-policy-website-terms-of-use/) | [Legal Notice](https://mobilecitizen.org/legal/)  
[Web Site Design & Development by Tiger Studios](https://tiger-studios.com/).
